milanicosmetics.com 2019-05-12

# Privacy Policy – Milani Cosmetics

**MILANI COSMETICS PRIVACY POLICY**

  1. ******Commitment to Privacy**

New Milani Group LLC(“Milani”) offers and maintains this website, located at [www.milanicosmetics.com](http://www.milanicosmetics.com/), including all of its subdomains and subparts (collectively, “our website”).   Milani respects the privacy of everyone who visits our website. Our Privacy Policy is an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our customers. This policy was developed to inform visitors to our website about how Milani handles and uses personal information. Privacy is important; we hope you take the time to read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

**By visiting milanicosmetics.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

We will regularly assess this policy against new technologies, business practices, and our customers' needs to ensure that you are informed to make choices about how to share and secure your personal data. If you have questions about this privacy statement, Milani’s information practices, or your dealings with Milani, please contact us ** ** at 1-800-726-4147 or Regulatory Department, 2516 E 49th St., Vernon, CA 90058 or email us at [customerservice@milanicosmetics.com](mailto:customerservice@milanicosmetics.com) .

  2. ******Collection Of Your Information**

When you visit our website, you may provide us with two types of information: 1) personally identifiable information that you voluntarily disclose so that we may provide products or services to you, such as when you register for an account or submit information needed to fill an order; and 2) website use information collected automatically as you browse our website.  By using our website or allowing someone to use our website on your behalf, you are consenting to our collection, use, disclosure, transfer, storage, retention, and eventual destruction in accordance with this Privacy Policy of any personally identifiable information or other information received by us as a result of such use.

**Personally Identifiable Information**   **You Provide Us**

Milani may collect personally identifiable information about you including without limitation your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address.  If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages, together with your email address, and our responses.  You can always choose not to provide Milani with your information even though it may be necessary to place an order or to take advantage of other website features.

**Website Use Automatic Information**  

We also collect certain data automatically that is sent to us from the computer, mobile device and/or browser through which you access our website (“Automatic Data”). This Automatic Data includes, without limitation, statistics on your activities on our website (such as the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our website), information about how you came to our website, and data collected through Cookies Web Logs or other similar technologies discussed in more detail in our Cookie Policy. Much of this Automatic Data is not personally identifiable information. However, when you register for our website or otherwise submit personally identifiable information to us, we may associate this Automatic Data with your personally identifiable information. At such time, we will treat any such combined data as personally identifiable information until such time as it can no longer be associated with you or used to identify you. 

  3. ******Use Of Your Information  **

Broadly speaking, we use personally identifiable information for the purpose for which you provided it.  Milani uses your name and address information only to fulfill customer needs, such as order fulfillment, billing, and delivery. If you send us an email, we may use your email address and other information you submit to provide customer service to you. 

We may also use your personally identifiable information or Automatic Data to administer our internal business activities, such as to design and arrange our website in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our website to better meet the needs of our customers and prospective customers, to better understand visitors to our website, to manage your account, to provide customer service, or to make available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers.

If you choose to receive email or text messages from Milani, we may use your personally identifiable information to send you information and updates about Milani cosmetic products, tips, promotional offers and giveaways, as well as changes to our Website, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. We will do this only with your permission.  If you do not wish to receive text messages from Milani, please text STOP to the last message received and you will be automatically removed. If you do not wish to receive email messages, please click the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email to be removed. If you are having any issues with opting out of communication, please email [customerservice@milanicosmetics.com](mailto:customerservice@milanicosmetics.com) for assistance.

You may notify us at any time of your desire not to receive these communications, or Opt Out, by clicking on a response box when you receive such an offer or by emailing your request to unsubscribe to: [customerservice@Milanicosmetics.com](mailto:customerservice@Milanicosmetics.com).

  4. ******Disclosure Of Your Information**

**No Sale of Your Information**

We are not in the business of selling your personally identifiable information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. Therefore, we will not sell your personally identifiable information to third parties, including third party advertisers. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may disclose, transfer, or share your personally identifiable information with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below.

**Sharing Information with Parent Companies, Subsidiaries, And Affiliates**

We may share your personally identifiable information with our parent companies, subsidiaries, and/or affiliates for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy. Our parent companies, subsidiaries, and affiliates will be bound to maintain that personally identifiable information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Sharing Information with Successors**

As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, personally identifiable information may be part of the transferred assets. You acknowledge and agree that any successor to or acquirer of Milani (or its assets) will continue to have the right to use your personally identifiable information and other information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Sharing Information with Agents, Consultants, and Related Third Parties**

We, like many businesses, sometimes engage other companies to perform certain business-related functions. These companies include our marketing agencies, database service providers, backup and disaster recovery service providers, email service providers, payment processors, and others.  When we engage another company to perform such functions, we may provide it with personally identifiable information, Automatic Data, or aggregate information about our customers, sales, website traffic patterns, and related website information, in connection with its performance of such functions.  However, Milani does not collect or store credit card information or internet protocol addresses directly; rather, we employ a third party payment processor who may collect, store, and use such information.  We take measures to select product or service providers that are responsible and afford privacy protections to their customers, such as those that comply with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards. However, we cannot make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies.

**Sharing Information**   **with Strategic Partners**

We may enter into strategic marketing alliances or partnerships with third parties for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you. In these circumstances, Milani may communicate with you on behalf of a strategic partner, but strategic partners will not be given access to your personal information. In connection with strategic marketing alliances or partnerships, we will retain all ownership rights to the information, and we will not share your personal information.

**Sharing Information through Social Media**

You may connect to Milani through your accounts on third party services like Facebook, Twitter, or Instagram, in which case we may collect, use, disclose, transfer, store, and retain information relating to your account with such third party services in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information**

We may disclose your personally identifiable information if required to do so by law (including without limitation, responding to a subpoena or request from law enforcement, a court, or a government agency) or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary (a) to comply with a legal obligation; (b) to protect or defend our rights, interests or property or that of third parties; (c) to prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with our website; (d) to act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of our website or the public; or (e) to protect against legal liability.

  5. ******Your Choices About Use and Disclosure Of Your Information**

People have different privacy concerns. Our goal is to be clear about what information we collect, so that you can make meaningful choices about how it is used.

You may choose to limit the personally identifiable information you submit by merely browsing our website without providing your name or other information.  If you do so, you may not be able to use certain functionality of our website.  To open an account, for example, you must provide your name and email address. 

Alternatively, you may choose to opt in or out of specific uses of your information.  You can view and edit your preferences about whether to receive email communications from Milani by accessing your account on the My Account page.  If you have registered to receive such email, you can opt out at any time by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any such email or by sending a request to unsubscribe by emailing your request  to: customerservice[@milanicosmetics.com](mailto:unsub@milanicosmetics.com).  Even after you opt out of all electronic communications, we will retain your personally identifiable information according to this Privacy Policy, but we will no longer use it to contact you.

  6. ******Information Security**

Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer information. When you place an order through our website, we encode your information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology. Our business practices also limit employee access to personally identifiable information and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes, and transactions.  You can help secure your information by protecting against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**Storage of Your Information**

We may store personally identifiable information itself or such information may be stored by third parties to whom we have transferred it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We take what we believe to be reasonable steps to protect the personally identifiably information collected via our website from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, inadvertent disclosure, alteration, and destruction. However, no network, server, database or Internet or e-mail transmission is ever fully secure or error free. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us electronically. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any personally identifiable information.

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**  

If you have registered for an account on our website, you may access and update some of your personally identifiable information being stored by us by logging in and visiting the My Account page.  You may also request access to all of your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing us at [customerservice@milanicosmetics.com](mailto:customerservice@milanicosmetics.com).  If you have not registered for an account on our website, you may create one by signing up, which will give you access to update some of your personally identifiable information directly. We will take reasonable steps to respond to requests relating to personally identifiable information within thirty (30) days, however, to the extent lawful, we may reject requests that we find to be unreasonable (i.e., require disproportionate efforts or material changes to our information systems), impractical, or abusive (i.e., repetitive requests, requests made in bad faith, requests that would compromise third party information).

**Information Retention**

We may retain your personally identifiable information as long as you continue to use our website. You may close your account by contacting us. However, we may retain personally identifiable information for an additional period as is permitted or required under applicable laws. Even if we delete your personally identifiable information, it may persist on backup or archival media for an additional period of time.

**  Evaluation of Information**  **Protection Practices**

This Privacy Policy is periodically reviewed for compliance with legal requirements, corporate policies, and procedures governing the security, confidentiality, and quality of our information.

  7. ******Cookies Web Logs, And Similar Technologies**

Please refer to our Cookie Policy, which is hereby incorporated by reference into this Privacy Policy, for more information about our use of these technologies.

  8. ******Exclusions Third Party Links**

 Our website may contain links to other websites not operated or controlled by us (the “Third Party Sites”).  These links are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our website. This Privacy Policy applies only to our website. The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from our website do not imply that we endorse or have reviewed the Third Party Sites. We are not responsible for the practices employed by the Third Party Sites linked to or from our website nor the information or content contained therein. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies. 

**Non-Personal Data**

When you interact with our website, we may also collect non-personal data. The limitations and requirements in this Privacy Policy on our collection, use, disclosure, transfer and storage/retention of personally identifiable information do not apply to non-personal data. The non-personal data we collect, include without limitation, Automatic Data, domain names of your Internet Service Provider, your approximate geographic location, a record of your usage of our website, the time of your usage and aggregated personally identifiable information, but only to the extent that the foregoing cannot be used to specifically identify you. However, if we combine non-personal data with personally identifiable information, we will treat the combined data as personally identifiable information.

**Aggregated Personal Data**

In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve visitors of our website, we may conduct research on our customer demographics, interests, and behavior based on personally identifiable information and other information that we have collected. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis and this aggregate information does not identify you personally and therefore is considered and treated as non-personal data under this Privacy Policy.

  9. ******Children**

Milani does not knowingly or intentionally collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13), and our website is neither directed nor targeted to children under thirteen (13) years of age.  If you are under the age of thirteen (13), please do not submit any personally identifiable information through our website.  We strongly encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's use of the Internet and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide personally identifiable information through our website without their permission.  If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of thirteen (13) has provided personally identifiable information to us through our website, please contact us at [customerservice@milanicosmetics.com](mailto:customerservice@milanicosmetics.com), and we will use reasonable efforts to delete such personally identifiable information from our website and our files.

  10. ******International Privacy Laws**

If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that you are sending information (including personally identifiable information) to the United States where our servers are located. That information may then be transferred within the United States or back out of the United States depending on the type of information and how it is stored by us. We will hold and process your personally identifiable information in accordance with privacy laws in the United States and this Privacy Policy. Please note that privacy laws in the United States may not be the same as, and in some cases may be less protective than, the privacy laws in your country, and while in the United States personally identifiable information may be subject to lawful access requests by government agencies.

  11. ******Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Our website and our business may change from time to time.  As a result, it may be necessary for us to make changes to this Privacy Policy.  Milani reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify or supplement this policy at any time. If a material change to the terms of this policy is made, Milani will post a notice on its homepage and a link to the new policy.  Modifications will be effective thirty (30) days following the date of posting such a notice or such other date as is communicated in any other notice to you.  Your continued use of our website following the effectiveness of any modifications to this Privacy Policy constitutes acceptance of those modifications. If any modification to this Privacy Policy is not acceptable to you, you should cease accessing, browsing, and otherwise using our website.  

  12. ******Dispute Resolution**

If you have a complaint about Milani’s privacy practices, you should write to us at Regulatory Department, 2111 East 49th Street, Vernon, California 90058 or email us at [customerservice@milanicosmetics.com](mailto:legal@milanicosmetics.com). We will take reasonable steps to work with you to attempt to resolve your complaint.

  13. ******Acceptance Of These Terms**

By using our website, you agree to this Privacy Policy and the Milani Terms and Conditions of Use. If you do not so agree, please do not use our website. If Milani changes this Privacy Policy or the Terms and Conditions of Use, your continued use of our website following the posting of such changes will signify your acceptance of those changes. By providing personally identifiable information to Milani, you fully and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of your information throughout the world, including, without limitation, in the United States and in other countries that may be considered as having less than adequate protection for your personally identifiable information.

**MILANI COSMETICS COOKIE POLICY**

This Cookie Policy sets forth our policy with respect to information, including information that can be associated with a specific person and could be used to identify that person (“personally identifiable information”), that is collected from visitors to our website through cookies, web logs, and other similar technologies.

  1. ******Incorporation By Reference**

Please also refer to our Privacy Policy, into which this Cookie Policy is incorporated by reference, which sets forth our policy with respect to the collection, use, disclosure, transfer, and storage of information, including personally identifiable information, that is collected from visitors to our website. Nothing in this Cookie Policy shall be deemed to modify, waive, amend, or rescind any other term of the Privacy Policy.

  2. ******Consent**

By using our website, you are consenting to the use of the technologies described in this Cookie Policy to collect both personally identifiable information and non-personal data and to the storage of information on your device or web browser as described in this Cookie Policy.

  3. ******What are cookies?**

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of information that is placed on your web browser when you access and/or use our website that stores text and can later be read back by our website or third parties. Cookies are used to recognize your browser and you as a unique visitor to our website. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one webpage to simplify subsequent interactions with that website by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user’s transactions on related webpages. This makes it easier for a user to move from one webpage to another and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.

  4. ******How can I manage cookies?**

Cookies may be session cookies (i.e., last only for one browser session) or persistent cookies (i.e., continue on your browser until they are affirmatively deleted). You can manage cookies through your web browser's option settings and through those settings you may be able (a) to receive notifications when you are receiving new cookies; (b) to disable cookies; or (c) to delete cookies. Please refer to your web browser's help section for information on how to do this.

  5. ******What does Milani use these technologies for?**

**Essential Uses**

We use these technologies in a way that is essential for the operation of our website or parts of our website. For example, we may use cookies to determine where to route your traffic to effectively distribute our website workload across numerous servers. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our website and evaluate our website’s visitor capacity.

**Performance/Analytics**

We use these technologies to monitor our website and to analyze how you use our website. We may place cookies that allow us to measure the time of your requests to our servers and our responses, to test new features, to record statistics about site usage, to track your activities on our website, and to track the places from which you come to our website. We may also use third party cookies to collect information about visitor behavior on our website for these Performance/Analytics purposes.

**Functionality**

We use these technologies to allow us to provide certain functionality on our website and to remember your preferences. For instance, cookies allow Milani to track your order history and returns, to auto-populate shipping and billing addresses, and to give you access to features such as a “Wish List.”

**Advertising (including behavioral/interest based advertising)**

In the future, we may use these technologies to deliver focused online banner advertisements to you both on and off our website. By using these technologies, we hope to better tailor these advertisements to your interests. Sometimes this is called online behavioral, interest based or retargeted advertising. Many of the third party technologies that enable this advertising participate in voluntary frameworks that allow you to opt-out of it.

Such third-party service providers include Criteo, Adroll, Rubicon, Google, Media Math, Perfect Audience, Quantcast, Retargeter, and Yahoo! among others.  You can control your preferences directly with each such third party service provider.

  6. ******Does anybody else use these technologies on your services?**

Most of the cookies and other technologies described above on our website are set by us (aka first party cookies) or are used in connection with our website and set by third party service providers at our direction ("Third Party Cookies"). We may use Third Party Cookies with respect to each of the uses set forth above.

 Last updated and effective: January 14, 2019
